<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Dingjia (Brian) Lin</title>
    <link>https://dingjia-lin.github.io/authors/author/</link>
      <atom:link href="https://dingjia-lin.github.io/authors/author/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description>Dingjia (Brian) Lin</description>
    <generator>Source Themes Academic (https://sourcethemes.com/academic/)</generator><language>en-us</language>
    <image>
      <url>https://dingjia-lin.github.io/img/icon-192.png</url>
      <title>Dingjia (Brian) Lin</title>
      <link>https://dingjia-lin.github.io/authors/author/</link>
    </image>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://dingjia-lin.github.io/authors/author/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://dingjia-lin.github.io/authors/author/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Dingjia (Brian) Lin (He, His, Him) is currently a PhD candidate in the Department of Electrical and Electronic Engineering at the University of Manchester. He holds two Master’s degrees, one in Mobile Communication and Smart Networking from the University of Southampton and another in Wireless Communication Systems from the University of Sheffield. He obtained his Bachelor’s degree in Communication Engineering from Chongqing University of Posts and Telecommunications.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;His research interests include non-orthogonal multiple access (NOMA), backscatter communication (BackCom), convex and non-convex optimization, cognitive radio, and fluid antenna systems. Dingjia has published multiple papers in prestigious journals and conferences, focusing on topics such as energy-efficiency maximization, beamforming, and uplink data rate optimization in NOMA systems.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In addition to his academic work, Dingjia is skilled in Python, MATLAB, and LaTeX, and is fluent in both English and Chinese. Outside of research, he enjoys photography, reading, and astronomical observation.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
